Manuel.
曼紐爾
Manuel!
曼紐爾！
l think. . . .
我想……
l think l found you one.
我給你找著了一個
Look, l called you, right?
這次我可是給你打電話了
Soon as l couldn't pull it out myself, l called you, John.
我一發現自己搞不定 就馬上給你打電話了，約翰
lt's okay, it's okay. We had to tie her down, okay?
別擔心，沒事的 我們必須得把她綁上，你明白嗎？
lt's okay.
沒事的
This is Constantine.
我是康斯坦丁
John Constantine, asshole.
約翰·康斯坦丁 你這混蛋
Sure.
當然
What the hell?
怎么了？
l need a mirror.
我需要一面鏡子
Now. At least 3 feet high.
快去拿！ 至少要3英尺高
Move! Go, now!
愣著干嘛，快去拿啊！
This is Kramer.
我是克雷默
Chas Kramer, asshole.
查斯·克雷默 你這混蛋
Asshole.
混蛋
What? Oh, this is Kramer. Chas Kramer, asshole.
什么？哦，我是克雷默 查斯·克雷默，混蛋
-Chas! -What?
- 查斯！ - 什么事？
-Move the car. -Why?
- 把車挪開 - 為什么？
Move the damn car!
叫你挪你就挪！
''Chas, move the car. ''
“查斯，把車挪開”
There, car's moved.
好吧，挪了
Lift it up over the bed.
把鏡子舉起來，對著床
Tie that end off. Hennessy, over the top.
把那頭系牢 亨內斯，從上面拉過去
Close your eyes. And whatever happens, don't look.
把你們的眼睛閉上 不管發生什么都別睜開
No!
不！
Show yourself.
現身吧
Smile pretty, you vain prick.
來笑一個，你這傻X
For your boss.
操你媽！
Pull it!
拉！
Ma? Ma?
媽媽？
Like l said, l found you something, didn't l, John? Didn't l?
我說得沒錯吧，約翰，給你找著一個 是不是？
What happened in there?
那儿怎么了？
Going to a lot of meetings, l see.
最近會議很多吧
Keeps the voices out so l can sleep.
鬧得我都睡不著
l have to sleep, John.
我得睡覺，約翰
l need some help, Father.
我需要幫助，神父
You do?
你？
From me?
要我幫助？
What kind of--?
什么樣的……？
-Hey, listen, l-- -That exorcism wasn't right.
- 听著，我…… - 你那种驅魔術不對
Listen to the ether.
听著廣播
Anything unusual, you let me know.
如果有什么异常，一定要告訴我
Come on, you don't need its protection. lt'll be like back in the day.
來吧，你不需要它的保護 它今天可能還會回來
A few days.
或許几天
Okay.
好吧
Okay. For you, John.
好吧，為了你，約翰
John, why would you do that if you know it's not my car?
約翰，你明知這不是我的車
-l told you to move it. -You did tell me to move it. . .
- 我告訴過你讓你挪開的 - 你是告訴過我
. . .but if you'd said you were dropping a 300-pound mirror with a demon. . .
可是如果你告訴我 你要扔下來一個裝著魔鬼的300磅的鏡子
. . .l would've moved it further, John.
我會把車挪得更遠一點
-Take Alvarado. -Yeah, thank you. l know what to take.
- 去阿爾瓦拉多大街 - 好的先生，我知道怎么走
You ever think if you told me more now that maybe l could help out?
你有沒有考慮過，如果多告訴我一些事情 說不定我能幫上忙呢？
-No? -Nope.
- 沒有？ - 沒有
Nope?
沒有？
Of course it's a nope.
當然是——沒有
Bless me, Father, for l have sinned.
保佑我，神父，我有罪
It's been...
我已經……
... two weeks since my last confession.
有兩個禮拜沒來忏悔了
l killed a man today.
今天我殺了個人
Another one.
又一個
l didn't even see his face, l just. . .
我甚至連他長什么樣都沒看清
. . .pulled the trigger, and he went away.
就扣下了扳机 接著他就死了
Most cops go 20 years without firing their guns.
大多數警察20年都不開一槍
Why do I always know where these guys are?
而我卻總是知道 這些家伙藏在哪儿
Where to aim, when to fire.
該朝哪儿瞄准，什么時候開槍
I'm wondering, is there something wrong with me, Father?
神父，我在想 會不會是我有什么問題？
Something damned?
被詛咒了？
God has a plan for you. He has a plan for us all.
上帝自有安排 他給我們每個人都安排好了
You mustn 't let your faith be overshadowed by guilt.
別讓罪惡吞沒了你的信念
Yeah, I'm trying.
是的，我在努力
I'm trying real hard.
一直都在努力
Isabel.
伊莎貝爾
Things l've beaten.
我所戰胜的東西
Things most people never even heard of.
大多數人听都沒听說過
And now l'm gonna be done in by this.
可是現在呢 我卻要被這玩意儿搞定
Wouldn't be the first, John.
你也不是第一個了，約翰
Come on, Les.
得了吧，萊絲
You saved me before, you can do it again, right?
你救過我一次 這次也可以，對嗎？
This is aggressive.
癌細胞已經擴散了
Twenty years ago, you didn't wanna be here.
20年前，你不想來這儿
Now you don't wanna leave.
現在你又不想离開
Yeah, that's a good idea.
你還抽
John, you really need to prepare.
約翰，你真的需要准備一下了
-Make arrangements. -No need.
- 安排后事吧 - 沒必要
l already know exactly where l'm going.
我很清楚自己何去何從
-Morning. -Good morning.
- 早 - 早上好
-Detective.
- 探長
-No, no, no. -Angela, wait.
- 不，不不 - 安吉拉，等等
You don't need to see this, okay? No.
你還是別看了，好嗎？別看了
Give us the room, please.
大家先回避一下
lsabel.
伊莎貝爾
She fell from the roof?
她從屋頂上掉下來的？
She jumped.
她跳下來的
-No. -Look. . .
- 不可能 - 听著
. . .l know it's hard to accept. She was sick.
我知道這很難接受 可她有病
-lsabel wouldn't kill herself. -Angie.
- 伊莎貝爾不會自殺的 - 安吉
-She wouldn't kill herself. -Detective.
- 她不會自殺的 - 探長
-Period.
- 皮瑞爾德
Period!
皮瑞爾德！
Angie, there were security cameras.
安吉，監控錄像都拍下來了
-Hold the door. You going down? -Not if l can help it.
- 等一下，是下去么？ - 如果我有辦法，當然不想“下去”
A new case?
有新案子？
The big score? The mother lode? The one you've been waiting for?
什么大案子？ 是你期待已久的嗎？
-Humor me. -Don't l always?
- 少奉承我 - 習慣了
Oh, yeah, that's-- Much obliged. Thank you.
哦，這是…… 太感激了，謝謝
How you feeling, John?
最近還好嗎，約翰？
So, what's new?
看看有什么新的貨色
Bullet shavings from the assassination attempt on the pope. . .
教皇遇刺時留下的子彈碎屑
. . .holy-water ampoules from the River Jordan. . .
采自約旦河的圣水針劑
. . .and-- Oh, you'll love this. --screech beetle from Amityville.
還有……哦，這個你肯定喜歡 從阿米蒂維勒村找來的尖叫甲虫 （譯者注：參考電影"The Amityville Horror"）
Yeah, it's funny to you, but to the fallen, that's like nails on a chalkboard.
是啊，對你來說很有趣 可對“下面”的東西來說，這就像黑板上釘釘
What is it, exactly, with you and bugs?
你和虫子，到底是什么關系？
l just like them.
我只是喜歡它們
Yeah. Who doesn't?
是啊，誰不喜歡？
Yeah, easy there, hero.
悠著點，大英雄
-That's dragon's breath. -l thought you couldn't get it anymore.
- 這是“龍之息” - 我還以為你再也搞不到了呢
Yeah, well, l know a guy who knows a guy.
是這樣，我朋友的朋友……
So, what's the action?
好吧，這次是什么行動？
l just pulled a soldier demon out of a little girl.
我剛把一個魔兵 從一個小女孩的身体里赶出來
Looked like it was trying to come through.
看起來好像它想要复活
Yeah, l know how it sounds.
我懂你的意思
No, we're finger puppets to them, John. . .
可是約翰，我們對他們來說 只不過是掌中的玩偶
. . .not doorways.
而不是某种入口
They can work us, but they can't come through onto our plane.
他們可以操縱我們 但不能穿透結界進到我們的世界中
Check the scrolls anyway. See if there's any precedent.
還是查一下卷軸吧 看看以前有沒有先例
Sure thing, John.
沒問題，約翰
Anything else?
還有什么事嗎？
Wouldn't happen to have anything for a--?
你那里有沒有什么可以……？
On the house.
免費的 （譯者注：止咳藥）
All right, question. How much longer do l have to be your slave, John?
好吧，我有個問題 我還得做你的奴隸到几時？
You're not my slave, Chas.
你不是我的奴隸，查斯
You're my very appreciated apprentice.
你是我非常賞識的徒弟
Like Tonto or Robin.
就像湯托和羅賓一樣
Or that skinny fellow with the fat friend.
還有那個胖哥身邊的小家伙
Right. So then why don't l apprentice something besides driving, then, John?
好吧，那我除了開車之外 就不能干點別的了么？
John? John.
約翰？約翰
l love our little talks, John.
很高興和你談話，約翰
May l take your coat, Mr. Constantine?
您的外套，康斯坦丁先生
No, thanks, l'm not gonna be staying long.
不用了，謝謝 我一會儿就走
-How about you, ma'am? -Oh, no, l'm not staying long either.
- 這位女士，您呢？ - 哦不用了，我也一會儿就走
l really need to speak with him. lt's important.
我真的要和他說話 有重要的事
First come, first served.
先到先得
So you're rude no matter where you are.
看來你到哪儿都是這么粗魯
-Father. -Hi.
- 神父 - 你好
-You have news. Yes. -Yes, l spoke with the bishop.
- 帶來什么新消息了 - 是的，剛和主教談過
l know what you want, son.
我知道你要什么，孩子
Still keeping your all-seeing eye on me, Gabriel?
你那雙無所不見的眼睛還盯著我呢 加百列？ （譯者注：替上帝把好消息報告世人的天使）
l'm flattered.
承蒙夸獎
Well, l could offer something. . .
我可以告訴你一些
. . .about how a shepherd leads even the most wayward of his flock. . .
關于牧羊人是怎樣 帶領他最不听話的羊群的故事
. . .but it might sound disingenuous.
可這听起來也許不夠真誠
She has to have a Catholic funeral, Father. She has to.
她應該得到天主教的葬禮 神父，求你了
-Angela, it's still considered a mortal sin. -She didn't commit suicide.
- 安杰拉，她犯的是不可饒恕的大罪 - 她不是自殺的
The bishop believes otherwise. You know the rules.
可主教不這么想 你知道教規的
Oh, rules.
哦，教規
Father.
神父
David.
戴維
This is lsabel.
她是伊莎貝爾
God was the only one she ever believed loved her.
她惟一相信的愛她的人就是上帝
Please.
求你了
l'm sorry.
恕我無能為力
l've been seeing some unusual soul traffic lately.
最近我看到一些异常的靈异活動
You might consider giving me an extension.
也許你能考慮再給我點時間
l could do your side some good these days.
我可以為你們這邊幫些忙
You still trying to buy your way into heaven?
你還在為進入天堂積德呢？
What about the minions l've sent back?
沒見我赶走多少小鬼嗎？
-That alone should guarantee my entry. -How many times have l told you?
- 光憑這個，就應該保證我能進天堂了 - 我跟你說過多少次了？
That's not the way this works.
靠這樣是進不了天堂的
Why, haven't l served him enough?
為什么？我為他做的還不夠多嗎？
-What does he want from me? -Only the usual.
- 他到底想要我怎么樣？ - 很簡單
Self-sacrifice, belief.
獻身，信仰
-Oh, l believe, for chrissake. -No, no, you know.
- 哦，我信！我對天發誓 - 不，不，你自己心里有數
And there's a difference. You've seen.
其中的區別你也能看見
l never asked to see. l was born with this curse.
我并沒有要求看見 我生下來就被詛咒了
A gift, John.
約翰，這是天賦
One that you've squandered on selfish endeavors.
而你只是用自私的行動把它浪費了
l'm pulling demons out of little girls.
我把魔鬼從女孩的身体里赶走
Who's that for?
這是為了誰？
Everything you've ever done, you've only ever done for yourself.
你所做的一切都是為了你自己
To earn your way back into his good graces.
為了積德好進入天堂
lmpossible rules, endless regulations. . .
不可能的規則，無盡的約束
. . .who goes up, who goes down and why.
誰上天，誰入地 為什么
You don't even understand us.
你一點都不理解我們
You're the one who should go to hell, half-breed.
你才應該入地獄 你這個雜种
Why me, Gabriel?
為什么是我，加百列？
lt's personal, isn't it?
這完全是因為我自己的緣故，是不是？
l didn't go to church enough, l didn't pray enough. . .
因為去教堂去得太少 也不怎么祈禱
. . .l was 5 bucks short in the collection plate. Why?
還舍不得往募捐箱里放上5塊錢 是不是？
You are going to die young. . .
你這么年輕就要死
. . .because you smoked 30 cigarettes a day since you were 1 5.
是因為你從15歲起就每天要吸30根煙
And you're going to go to hell. . .
而你之所以要去地獄
. . .because of the life you took.
是因為你所過的生活
You're fucked.
你很失敗
At least it's nice out.
至少在外面感覺還不錯
He always had a rotten sense of humor.
他總是一點幽默感都沒有
And his punch lines are killers.
他的笑話一點都不好笑
John!
約翰！
Constantine, it's raining! John! Hey!
康斯坦丁，下雨哪！ 約翰，嗨！
Twenty-two women were found buried in the assailant's back yard.
凶手的后院里發現埋藏著22具女尸
So much damage had been done to the bodies, police had to match....
尸体受到嚴重的摧殘 警察的辨認工作……
Police report she had been physically penetrated...
据警察說 她的身体曾被穿刺超過100次
...over 1 00 times and buried alive.
然后被活埋
--found locked in a storage freezer, his head severed and his organs....
……被發現鎖在冷藏庫中 頭部嚴重受傷，器官……
He stuffed Holly's body into....
他把霍莉的身体塞入……
-The bodies ravished by the unknown.... -He used a small handsaw....
- 受到不明強暴的尸体…… - 他使用了一把小手鋸……
Had nearly decapitated.... Even his eyes were gouged out.
頭顱几乎被砍下來…… 眼珠都被挖了出來
Isabel.
伊莎貝爾
l'm so sorry, lzzy.
我很抱歉，妹妹
Constantine.
康斯坦丁
Dodson.
道森
Hello?
喂？
Hello.
喂
Hey. Hey, buddy, got a light?
嗨，老兄 能借個火嗎
Should've minded your own business, exorcist.
別多管閒事，驅魔人
l know where you're going, John. You're going to Midnite's.
我知道你要去哪儿，約翰 你要去米耐那儿
You're supposed to wait in the cab.
希望你呆在車里
lt's a haven for those who rise and fall. l remember reading about this, John.
那儿是鬼魂的避難所 我記得在書上讀到過，約翰
-You read too much, kid. lt's a bar. -lt's a bar?
- 你讀書讀得太多了，那是個酒吧 - 酒吧？
lt's a bar. Papa Midnite is a crusader for good. He swore the oath of neutrality.
是酒吧，米耐老爹是個樂善好施的人 他曾經發誓堅守中立
-John, the man's a legend. -Yeah.
- 約翰，他可是傳奇人物 - 是的
Can you please get me into this bar, John, please?
你能帶我進去嗎？ 約翰，求求你
l'm begging you, John, please?
求你了，約翰，行嗎？
-Sure, you can get in. -l can get in?
- 好吧，你可以進去 - 我可以進去？
lf you can get in.
如果你能進去的話
lf l can get--? lt's a bear, though, right? Or two ducks in a cloud?
如果我能……？ 是熊？還是云中的兩只鴨子？
Two frogs on a bench.
長凳上的兩只青蛙
No, no, l'm with the guy you just--
不，我是和剛才那個人一起的……
John! John!
約翰！約翰！
l'm with him, though.
我是和他一起的
Rat in a dress.
穿著裙子的老鼠
Of course it is. Rat in a dress.
當然，穿著裙子的老鼠
l'm just testing. l'm just testing.
我只是試試，只是試試
Don't get up.
不用站起來了
You've been absent some time.
好久不見了
Have you come here with relics to sell?
又有什么圣物要賣嗎？
No, l'm out of that now. l've been too busy.
沒有，現在不干那個了 太忙了
Perhaps peddling forgeries has ended up being bad for your health.
終于發現造假對你的健康不利了？
Midnite, Jesus. . .
米耐，上帝啊……
. . .l thought the thing was authentic.
……我想這件事是真的
l see now.
我知道了
Your health is bad for other reasons. How long?
你的身体不好是因為其他原因 多長時間了？
A few months, maybe a year.
几個月吧，可能一年
l thought l heard thunder last night.
我昨晚好像听到雷聲了
Must have been Satan's stomach growling.
肯定是撒旦的胃在咆哮
You're the one soul he'd come up here himself to collect.
你的魂要他親自出馬來收
So l've heard.
我也听說了
Well, l am most certain you did not come here. . .
好吧，我想你來這儿
. . .for a sympathetic shoulder to cry on.
肯定不是想找個有同情心的人來訴苦的
A demon just attacked me, right out in the open on Figueroa.
剛才有個魔鬼攻擊了我 就在通往費格羅阿大街的路上
They don't like you, John.
他們不喜歡你，約翰
How many have you deported back to hell?
你驅赶了多少個魔鬼？
Not some angry half-breed, Midnite. A full-fledged demon, here, on our plane.
米耐，這次不是那种憤怒的雜种 而是實實在在的魔鬼，就在這儿，在我們的世界里
Clearly l do not have to remind you that is impossible.
我想我不用提醒你 這是不可能的
And yesterday l saw a soldier demon. . .
還有昨天，我見到一個魔兵
. . .trying to chew its way out through a little girl.
試圖從一個小女孩身体里沖破結界
Listen, John, demons stay in hell, angels in heaven. . .
听著，約翰，魔鬼只能呆在地獄里 天使只能呆在天堂里
. . .the great detente of the original superpowers.
從造物之初就是這樣
Thanks for the history lesson, Midnite. You've been a tremendous help.
謝謝你給我上的歷史課，米耐 你真是幫了我大忙了
Now. . .
現在
. . .l need to use the chair.
我需要使用那把椅子
John, forgetting the fact that it would almost certainly kill you. . .
約翰，你難道忘了 這么做几乎肯定是要沒命的
. . .you know l am neutral.
你知道我是中立者
And as long as the balance is maintained, l take no sides.
只要平衡沒有發生變化 我就保持中立
Before you were a bartender. . .
在你當酒吧侍應之前
. . .you were one witch doctor against, what, 30 Ashgar?
你曾經是個巫醫
-And l-- -You were Constantine.
- 而我…… - 你是康斯坦丁
The John Constantine.
約翰·康斯坦丁
Once.
曾經是的
This isn't the usual game, l can feel it.
這次非比尋常，我能感覺得到
Something's coming.
它在逼近
Spooky.
膽小鬼
Balthazar.
巴爾薩澤
That expression alone has made my entire night.
光是那种表情就讓我徹夜難眠
l'll make your night.
我來教你怎么睡覺
l'll deport your sorry ass right where you stand, you half-breed shit!
我現在就把你打回老家去 你這個雜碎！
You know the rules of my house. While here, you will abide by them.
你知道我這儿的規矩 在我這儿就要按我的規矩來
Johnny boy.
小約翰
Word is you're on your way down.
听說你快要下來了
Fresh meat.
新鮮的肉啊
Finger-licking good.
吮指回味
We have a meeting now, John.
約翰，我們還有事要談
What? l didn't catch that.
你說什么？我沒听清
Welcome to my life.
歡迎加入我的生活
Mr. Constantine.
康斯坦丁先生
-l saw you-- -l remember.
- 我們之前…… - 我記得
-And then l saw you at the-- -Regular kismet.
- 后來還在…… - 看來咱們還真是有緣
l'd like to ask you a few questions, if that would be okay.
能不能容我問几個問題
l'm not really in the talking mood right now.
現在我不想和任何人說話
Well, maybe you could just listen then.
好吧，那光听我說可以嗎？
Please?
行嗎？
Always a catch.
就知道沒那么簡單
My sister was murdered yesterday.
昨天我妹妹被謀殺了
-Sorry to hear. -Thanks.
- 很遺憾 - 謝了
She was a patient at Ravenscar. She jumped off the roof.
她是雷文斯卡精神病院的病人 從屋頂跳下去死的
Thought you said she was murdered.
剛才好像听你說是謀殺？
Yeah, well, lsabel wouldn't have taken her own life.
是的，伊莎貝爾不可能自殺的
Yeah, what kind of mental patient kills herself?
也是，什么樣的精神病人會自殺呢？
That's just crazy.
真可怕
Look, l've heard your name around the precinct.
是這樣的，我听說你在這塊很有名
l know the circles you travel in. The occult, demonology, exorcisms.
我知道你活動的圈子 超自然，鬼神學，驅魔……
Just before my sister was committed, she became deeply paranoid.
就在我妹妹被殺之前 她得了嚴重的妄想症
She started talking about demons, angels.
她開始談論魔鬼，天使
Now, l think someone got to her, Mr. Constantine.
我想她是被什么人影響了 康斯坦丁先生
l think they brainwashed her into stepping off that roof.
她肯定是被洗了腦 才會從屋頂上跳下去的
Some kind of legion or cult.
某种邪教組織
Sounds like a theory, detective.
你分析得很有道理啊 大偵探
Good luck.
祝你好運
l thought with your background, you could at least. . .
我想以你的背景 至少可以……
. . .point me in the right direction.
給我指明正确的方向
Yeah, okay, sure.
可以，當然可以
lt wasn't a suicide.
她不是自殺
My sister was a devout Catholic.
我妹妹是個虔誠的天主教徒
Do you understand that? lf she took her own life--
你懂嗎？ 如果她自己結束自己的生命
Her soul would go straight to hell. . .
她的靈魂會直接下地獄
. . .where she'd be ripped apart over and over in screaming, brutal agony. . .
在尖叫中一次又一次地被撕裂 飽受折磨，极度痛苦
. . .for all eternity. That it?
永世不得翻身，對嗎？
That about right?
我說得沒錯吧？
Goddamn you.
你他媽的
Detective.
偵探
What if l told you that God and the devil made a wager. . .
如果我告訴你 上帝和魔鬼打了個賭……
. . .a kind of standing bet for the souls of all mankind?
他們的賭注就是所有人類的靈魂 你信么？
l'd tell you to stay on your meds.
我會告訴你回去找你的醫生
Humor me. No direct contact with humans. That would be the rule.
別跟我爭 他們的約定是不能直接涉足人間
-Just influence. See who would win. -Okay, l'm humoring you.
- 只能施加影響，最后看誰能贏 - 好吧，我不跟你爭
-Why? -Who knows.
- 可是為什么呢？ - 誰知道呢
-Maybe just for the fun of it. No telling. -Oh, so it's fun.
- 也許只是為了好玩 - 哦，這可真好玩
lt's fun when a man beats his wife to death, when a mother drowns her baby.
丈夫打死妻子好玩么？ 母親淹死孩子好玩么？
And you think the devil is responsible?
你覺得這都歸因于魔鬼？
People are evil, Mr. Constantine. People.
你錯了，康斯坦丁 是人，人才是魔鬼
You're right. We're born capable of terrible things.
你說得很對 人性本惡
Then sometimes something else comes along and gives us just the right nudge.
再加上受到其他某种東西的引導……
Well, this has been real educational. . .
好吧，謝謝你給我上了一課
. . .but l don't believe in the devil.
可我不相信有什么魔鬼
You should. He believes in you.
你應該相信 就如魔鬼相信你的存在
lt's a power outage.
只是停電了
Not likely.
不像
-What? -We should go. Now.
- 什么？ - 不能呆在這儿了，快走
What is that?
那是什么？
Wings.
翅膀
Maybe talons.
也許是魔爪
You're kidding. Of what?
別開玩笑了，你說什么？
Something that's not supposed to be here.
一些不該在這儿的東西
That's really not going to help.
槍在這儿基本上沒用
-Close your eyes. -Why?
- 閉上眼睛 - 為什么？
Suit yourself.
為了你自己
Demons stay in hell, huh?
誰說魔鬼只呆在地獄里？
Tell them that.
得告訴他們
Don't worry. Happens to everyone the first time.
別擔心 第一次都是這樣
lt's the sulfur.
那是硫磺
Sulfur.
硫磺
What were those things?
那些東西是什么？
Demons.
魔鬼
-Scavengers of the damned. -No, no. lt's impossible.
- 被詛咒的食腐怪 - 不，這不可能
Yeah. And l don't think they were after me.
信不信由你 而且我認為它們不是來找我的
You really believe she wouldn't commit suicide.
你真的認為她不是自殺的？
lsabel?
伊莎貝爾？
Never in a million years.
絕對不信
Well, let's be sure.
好吧，我們來确認一下
Let's see if she's in hell.
看看她是不是在地獄里
Oh, was it supposed to be hot or cold?
哦，應該是冷水還是熱水？
ln front of the chair.
放在椅子前面
l can't believe l'm doing this.
真不敢相信我居然在干這個
-These are all lsabel's things? -Yeah.
- 這些都是伊莎貝爾的東西？ - 對
-How about the cat? -Duck?
- 這貓呢？ - 達珂？
Yeah, why?
是啊，怎么了？
Duck.
達珂
Oh, you think that's strange.
哦，覺得奇怪是么
Cats are good.
貓是很好的動物
Half in, half out anyway.
很有靈性
lf this is some kind of spell or something. . .
如果你要施某种法術或什么的話
. . .don't you need candles and a pentagram for it to work?
難道不需要點蜡燭和畫五角星么？
Why, do you have any?
哦？你有嗎？
-This is crazy. -Yes.
- 簡直是瘋了 - 是的
l need you to leave.
你得离開
-l'm sorry? -Angela, please.
- 為什么？ - 安吉拉，拜托
The apartment.
我是說离開這屋子
Okay.
好吧
Be careful with that cat.
當心我的貓
God, l hate this part.
上帝，我恨干這個
-lsabel. -Constantine.
- 伊莎貝爾 - 康斯坦丁
Angela.
安吉拉
Jesus.
上帝
-Constantine, what--? -Twins.
- 康斯坦丁，你怎么啦？ - 雙胞胎
Jesus. What?
上帝，你說什么？
-You were twins. -What did you say?
- 你們是雙胞胎 - 你說什么？
-She killed herself. -What?
- 她是自殺的 - 什么？
And she's damned for it.
因此被罰入地獄
How is this possible?
這怎么可能？
l need to eat.
我得吃點東西
Hey! Hey, what are you doing in here?
嗨，嗨！ 你在這儿干什么？
Relax, man.
別激動，哥們儿
Slow down!
慢點！
What the hell kind of place is this?
這儿他媽的是什么地方？
John.
約翰
When l was a kid, l could see things.
我小的時候 能看到一些東西
Things humans aren't supposed to see.
一些人類看不到的東西
Things you shouldn 't have to see.
也是不應該看到的東西
My parents were normal. They did what most parents would do.
我父母都是正常人 他們像大多數父母一樣
They made it worse.
讓情況變得更糟
You think you're crazy long enough. . .
當你覺得再也無法忍受的時候
. . .you find a way out.
你就會尋找出路
-You tried to kill yourself. -I didn 't try anything.
- 你嘗試自殺？ - 我什么都沒嘗試
Officially, I was dead for two minutes.
准确的說，我死過兩分鐘
But when you cross over. . .
但是當我跨入另一個世界的時候
. . .time stops.
時間就停止了
Take it from me, two minutes in hell is a lifetime.
我敢說 地獄里的兩分鐘就像一生那么漫長
When l came back. . .
當我重回人世的時候
. . .l knew. . .
我終于知道
. . .all the things l could see were real.
我能看到的所有的東西都是真實的
Heaven and hell are right here. Behind every wall, every window.
天堂和地獄無處不在 每一堵牆，每一扇窗后面
The world behind the world, and we're smack in the middle.
這個世界背后還有一個世界 而我們被夾在中間
Angels and demons can't cross over onto our plane.
天使和魔鬼都不能逾越 進入我們的世界
So instead we get what l call half-breeds.
所以，我們看到的就是所謂的“雜种”
The influence peddlers.
蠱惑者
They can only whisper in our ears, but a single word can give you courage...
它們只能在你耳邊煽風點火 但是它的一句話就能給你勇气
...or turn your favorite pleasure into your worst nightmare.
或者讓你一下子從快樂的巔峰 掉落到痛苦的深淵
Those with the demon 's touch...
那些被魔鬼触碰的
...like those part angel, living alongside us.
比如半天使 是和我們生活在一起的
They call it the balance.
他們稱之為平衡
l call it hypocritical bullshit.
而我稱之為虛偽的狗屁
So when a half-breed breaks the rules. . .
所以當哪個雜种不守規矩
. . .l deport their sorry ass straight back to hell.
我會直接讓他滾進地獄
l don't get them all. . .
這樣的雜种太多了
. . .but l've been hoping to get enough to ensure my. . .
我只希望盡量多的除掉一些 讓自己能夠
-. . .retirement. -l don't understand.
- 早點退休 - 我不懂
l'm a suicide, Angela.
我就是在自殺，安吉拉
When l die, the rules say l've got just one place to go.
當我死的時候，按照規則 我只有一個地方可去
You're trying to buy your way into heaven.
你是在積德，希望能進天堂
What would you do if you were sentenced to a prison. . .
要是你被關進一個 半數犯人都是你親手抓進去的監獄里
. . .where half the inmates were put there by you?
你會有什么感覺？
l guess God has a plan for all of us.
我想上帝為我們每個人都安排好了一切
God's a kid with an ant farm, lady.
小姐 上帝只是一個玩螞蟻的小孩
He's not planning anything.
他什么都沒安排
When we were little. . .
在我們小的時候
. . .lsabel saw things too.
伊莎貝爾也能看到東西
Dodson.
道森
Guard spotted him groping the body, then he ran across the street.
警衛發現他在摸弄尸体 然后他倉皇跑到街對面
Came in here, and he had a go at the entire stock.
跑進店里來 把貨架上的酒打開喝了個遍
He drowned himself in alcohol in under a minute.
不到一分鐘 他就溺死在酒里了
Could've been a member of my fraternity.
本可以成為我們教友會的一員的
Hey, what the hell is he doing here?
他跑到這儿來干什么？
He's okay.
沒關系
Why didn't you call me, you son of a bitch?
為什么不給我打電話 狗娘養的
Yes?
喂？
What do you mean?
什么意思？
What?
什么？
How?
怎么會？
Got it. Bye.
知道了，拜拜
l need to see where lsabel died.
我要看一下伊莎貝爾死亡的現場
Seances, Ouija boards, channeling.
請神，占卜，通靈
Our father thought she was just trying to get attention.
父親以為她只是想引人注意
She certainly did that.
可事實上不是
She'd tell everyone about the things she said she saw.
她把她看到的東西告訴每一個人
She'd scare my mother half to death.
把母親嚇得半死
And then she stopped talking for almost a year.
之后几乎一年 她始終一言不發
So you had her committed.
所以你們把她送到這儿來了
Yeah.
是的
How long?
有多長時間了？
Two weeks.
兩個星期
This time.
這一次
She'd get better, and then she'd get worse. Recently, a lot worse.
她的病情時好時坏 最近又惡化了
That symbol that was cut in the dead guy's hand. . .
那個死者手掌上刻的符號
. . .does it have something to do with this?
會不會和這有關？
l'm a cop, John, remember?
約翰，別忘了我是警察
You don't walk off the roof of a building without leaving something behind.
一個人不可能什么都沒留下 就這么跳樓自殺的
And l showed you everything she left behind in that box, but feel free.
而我已經把她所有的遺物都給你看過了 不過你盡管找
Maybe she left something else. Not something a cop would find.
也許她留下了一些 警察找不到的東西
Something just for you.
一些只有你才能找到的東西
You were her twin, Angela. Twins tend to think alike.
你們是雙胞胎，安吉拉 雙胞胎的想法是相似的
-l'm not like my sister. -But you were once.
- 我不像我的妹妹 - 但你曾經是的
When you were kids.
當你們還是孩子的時候
When you'd spend every second with each other.
當你們每時每刻形影不离的時候
You'd start a sentence, she'd finish it. You'd get hurt, she'd cry.
你說一句，她就能接下句 你受傷了，她就會哭
That was a long time ago.
那是很久以前了
That kind of bond doesn't just disappear.
那种聯系不會這么輕易就消失的
There is nothing here.
這儿什么都沒有
-Hey. Come on. -She planned her death in this room.
- 得了吧 - 她在這間屋子里籌划了自己的死
She thought it up right here. Right where you're standing.
她是在這儿想出來的 就在你所站的地方
She knew you'd come. She counted on you to see what she saw. . .
她知道你會來 她指望你能見她所見
. . .feel what she felt, know what she knew.
感她所感 知她所知
-What did she do, Angela? -How should l know?
- 安吉拉，她做了什么？ - 我怎么會知道？
-l don't know.
- 我不知道
-What would you do?
- 換了你會怎么做？
What did she do, Angela? You know what she did. What did she do, Angela?
安吉拉，她做了什么？ 你知道的，她到底做了什么？
You know what she did. What are you afraid of? What did she do?
你知道的！ 你為什么不敢說？她做了什么？
-What did she do? -l don't know!
- 她做了什么？ - 我不知道！
When we were girls. . .
我們小的時候
. . .we would leave each other messages.
喜歡互相給對方留密信
ln light.
用光
ln breath.
或者在窗戶上
On the windows.
用嘴哈气
John, there is no 1 7th act in Corinthians.
約翰，歌林多書中沒有17章啊
Corinthians goes to 21 acts in the Bible in hell.
地獄圣經里，歌林多書有21章
They have Bibles in hell.
地獄里也有圣經
Paints a different view of Revelations.
描繪了另一幅“啟示錄”
Says the world will not end by God's hand...
地獄圣經中說 世界不會在上帝的手中終結
...but be reborn in the embrace of the damned.
而是會在黑暗中重生
Though if you ask me...
到那時……
. . .fire's fire.
就是人間煉獄了
1 6:29, 1 6:30.
16章29節，16章30節
Oh, my, this is certainly not good.
哦，天哪 果然不妙
''The sins of the father would only be exceeded by the sins of the son. ''
“子之罪定會超越父之罪”
-Whose son? -But he can't cross over, B.
- 誰的儿子？ - 但是他不可能逾越結界
-lmpossible to cross over. -Whose son? God's son?
- 結界是不可能逾越的 - 誰的儿子？上帝的儿子？
No, the other one. Devil had a son too.
不，是另一個 魔鬼也有儿子
Here it is.
在這儿
This is the sign of Mammon. . .
這是魔鬼之子曼蒙的標志
. . .the son of the devil. Well, hold on, it says here--
哦等一下，這儿說……
-Beeman? -Yeah.
- 比曼？ - 在
Sorry, l'm-- l'm sorry, no, l'm right here.
抱歉，我…… 抱歉，不，我在
lt says Mammon has no patience for his father's rule. . .
上面說曼蒙對他父親的規矩不耐煩了
. . .and yearns to forge his own kingdom of fire and blood.
渴望建立一個屬于他自己的 火与血的王國
Yeah. Mammon would be the last demon. . .
沒錯，曼蒙是我們最不愿意見到
. . .we'd ever want crossing over to our plane.
出現在我們世界里的魔鬼
No, wait, wait, wait. l'm reading. Seems to be a loophole.
等等，等等，听我讀下去 可是似乎存在某种漏洞
Always a catch.
就知道沒那么簡單
lt says first Mammon would have to possess a very, very powerful psychic.
這里說到 曼蒙首先要附身于一個非常強大的通靈者
-lsabel. -But that wouldn 't be enough.
- 伊莎貝爾 - 但這還不夠
To cross over, Mammon would need divine assistance.
要穿越結界 曼蒙還需要神的協助
the help of God.
也就是說需要上帝的幫助
-The help of God? -It says--
- 上帝的幫助？ - 上面說……
-Beeman? -John, look. . .
- 比曼？ - 約翰，听著
. . .l know you've never had much faith, you've never had much reason to. . .
我知道你從來都沒有什么信念 你從來都不愿意……
...but that doesn 't mean that we don 't have faith...
可這并不意味著你的心里
. . .in you.
不存在信念
Beeman? Beeman?
比曼？比曼？
Drive. Fast.
開快點
Beeman!
比曼！
Sulfur.
硫磺
Wasn't just lsabel.
不只是伊莎貝爾
l used to see things too.
我以前也能見到東西
But. . .
可是……
-. . .you already knew that, didn't you? -Go home, Angela.
- 你已經知道了，是不是？ - 回家去，安吉拉
l need to understand.
我要把事情搞清楚
You don't wanna know what's out there, trust me.
這些事情你最好不要知道 相信我
l'm stronger than lsabel.
我比伊莎貝爾強
Your sister embraced her gift, you denied yours. Denial is a better idea.
你的妹妹接受了她的天賦 而你拒絕了，還是拒絕比較好
lt's why you're still alive. Stick with me, that will change.
這也是為什么你還活著的原因 如果你繼續跟著我，就難說了
l don't need another ghost following me.
我不想再多個鬼魂跟著我
John, they killed my sister.
約翰，他們殺了我妹妹！
l'd trade places with her if l could.
我宁愿死的那個是我
l used to pretend that l didn't.
我過去一直假裝自己沒有這种能力
That l didn't see things.
什么都看不見
And. . .
然后
. . .by the time we were 1 0, they started forcing her to take. . .
到我們10歲的時候 父母開始強迫她吃安定藥
. . .antipsychotics. . .
并且接受治療
. . .and have treatments. They would come for her. . .
當那些東西出現的時候
. . .and she'd look at me, and she'd say to me, ''Tell them.
她總是看著我 對我說：“告訴他們啊”
Why don't you tell them, Angie, that you can see them too?''
“安吉，為什么你不告訴他們 你也能看見？”
But l lied.
可我卻撒了謊
l said:
我說：
''l don't see anything. ''
“我什么都沒看見”
Until one day. . .
直到有一天
. . .l finally stopped seeing.
我終于真的看不見了
l abandoned her, John.
我拋棄了她，約翰
l left her all alone.
我讓她孤立無援
l need to see what she saw.
我必須得看到她所看到的東西
Please.
請你幫幫我
You do this, there's no turning back.
這么做，可就沒法回頭了
You see them. . .
你看見了他們
. . .they see you.
他們也看見了你
Understand?
明白嗎？
Yeah.
明白
Sure.
好吧
So do l have to take the rest of my clothes off, or can l leave them on?
我必須把所有的衣服都脫了么？ 還是可以穿著？
John?
約翰？
l'm thinking.
我在考慮
On is fine.
穿著吧
-So why water? -lt's a universal conduit.
- 為什么用水？ - 水是万能的通道
Lubricates the transition from one plane to another.
可以幫助穿越結界
-Now ask me if there's water in hell. -ls there water in hell?
- 接著問我地獄里有沒有水 - 地獄里有沒有水？
Sit.
坐下
Normally, only a portion of the body has to be suspended. . .
通常只要身体的一部分浸入水中就可以了
. . .but you wanted the crash course.
但是你想來個速成的
Yeah, l wanted the crash course.
是的，我要速成的
So. . . .
那么……
So, what's gonna happen?
那會怎么樣？
Lie down.
躺下
-What do you mean lie down? -You have to be fully submerged.
- 躺下？什么意思？ - 你必須完全浸入水中
For how long?
要多長時間？
As long as it takes.
能堅持多久就多久
Take a deep one.
深吸一口气
Oh, God.
哦，上帝
Oh, God, all those people.
哦，上帝，所有這些人
Oh, lsabel.
哦，伊莎貝爾
l've always known.
我總是知道
l've always known where they are. l've always known where to find them. . .
我總是知道它們在哪儿 我總是知道如何找到它們
. . .where to aim and where to duck. . .
朝哪儿瞄准，在哪儿躲避
. . .and l've always known where they were.
我總是知道它們在哪儿
l've always known that it wasn't luck.
我知道那不是運气
Always known that it wasn't luck. l've always known. . . .
我一直都知道……
l've always known that l could see.
我一直都知道我能看見
Angela.
安吉拉
Someone was here.
有人來過
lt was his.
那是他留下的
Rolling.
轉動著
Not a ball.
不是球
Something smaller.
是某种小一點的東西
Shiny.
閃著光
Balthazar.
巴爾薩澤
Sorry.
對不起
Can you just kill him?
要殺了他嗎？？
What about the balance?
那平衡怎么辦？
Half-breed tipped the scales when he started killing my friends.
當這些雜种開始殺我朋友的時候 平衡就已經被破坏了
l'm just adding some counterweight.
我只是在天平的另一邊加些砝碼而已
John, l really want--
約翰，我真的很想……
Think of it as a bulletproof vest.
把它當作防彈衣
l'm coming with you.
我要和你一起去
You're staying in the car.
你得呆在車里
Fire? l was born of this.
火？我就是火里生的
How's Mammon crossing over, you half-breed piece of shit?
你這個爛雜种，告訴我 曼蒙到底要怎樣跨越結界？
That's better. Au naturel.
這樣更好，更自然
''Stay in the car. ''
“呆在車里”
''Wait here. ''
“在這儿等”
Men.
受不了你
Don't fight it, Johnny boy.
別抗拒，小約翰
Enjoy it.
好好享受
We'll see you very soon.
我們馬上就能見到你了
Not really, no.
你說錯了
You can't cheat it this time. You're going back to hell.
這回你跑不掉的 你會回到地獄里去
True.
沒錯
But you're not.
可你卻回不去了
-What are you doing? -l'm reading you your last rites.
- 你要干嘛？ - 我要給你做最后的超度
Spare me your remedial incantations.
別對我用治療咒語
You do know what it is to truly be forgiven?
你想知道真正被寬恕以后 會是什么樣嗎？
To be welcomed into the Kingdom of God.
被接納進入神的王國
Demon in heaven.
天堂里的魔鬼
l'd love to be a fly on that wall.
真想看看那時的情景
You're not a priest. You have no power.
你不是牧師，你沒有法力
Just tell me how Mammon is crossing over. . .
那你告訴我曼蒙打算怎樣沖破結界
. . .and you can go back to your shithole.
我就讓你滾回你的狗窩去
Okay, Bally, enjoy it.
好啊，不說是吧
''May God have mercy on you and grant you the pardon of all your sins.
“愿主怜憫你，饒恕你所有的罪孽”
Whose soever sins you remit on Earth, they are remitted unto them in heaven. ''
“不管犯下什么樣的罪孽 都饒恕你，讓你升入天堂”
-How? How's he doing it? -No.
- 快說，他要怎樣沖破結界？ - 不
No, l can't.
不，我不能說
Grant your child entry into thy kingdom. . .
“讓你的子民找到通往天國的大門……”
. . .in the name of the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit.
“以圣父、圣子和圣靈之名”
Amen!
阿門！
The blood of God.
上帝的血
He found it.
他找到了
Whatever killed the son of God. . .
只要殺死了上帝之子
. . .will give birth to the son of the devil.
就能讓魔鬼之子复活
By the way. . .
順便說一句
. . .you have to ask for absolution to be forgiven. . .
只有經過赦免才能得到寬恕
. . .asshole.
笨蛋
My work here is done.
我的任務已經完成了
-What are you laughing at? -She was my only mission. . .
- 你笑什么？ - 我的任務就是她
. . .and you brought her right to us.
而你正好把她帶來了
So does this walking fast mean you've found something?
干嘛走這么快 是不是發現了什么？
Jesus didn't die from being nailed to a cross. He was killed by a soldier's spear.
耶穌不是在十字架上被釘死的 而是被一個戰士的矛刺死的
The Spear of Destiny.
命運之矛
l'm a Catholic, John. l know the Crucifixion story.
我是個天主教徒，約翰 我知道耶穌受難的故事
l drew out the sister as you asked.
按您的吩咐，我引出了她的姐姐
She's been made flush and ready.
她的靈力已經被喚醒
So much power.
好強的能量
Now, if you grant me my resurrection, l shall serve.
如果您能讓我复活 我愿意為您效忠
Wait. But l did as we agreed.
等等，我們說好的
No. Please. No!
不，不！
Beeman said Mammon needed divine assistance to cross over.
比曼說過 曼蒙需要神的幫助才能跨越結界
How's the blood of God's only son?
看來那就是上帝唯一的儿子的血
The stains on the spear.
矛上的血跡
-Yeah. -So he gets the spear.
- 是的 - 那么說他找到了矛
He still has to locate a powerful psychic.
他還要找一個很強的通靈者
Not really.
已經有了
Twins.
雙胞胎
Where's the amulet?
護身符呢？
l don't know, l must have left it in the--
我不知道 肯定是落在車上了
What's wrong?
怎么了？
l don't know, l just feel--
我不知道，只是覺得……
-Bird on a ladder. -Sorry.
- 梯子上的鳥 - 抱歉
-Wait here. -Yeah.
- 在這儿等 - 好的
Who's a rat in a dress now, huh, bitch?
現在誰是穿裙子的老鼠了？啊？ 狗娘養的
Have you lost what little mind you have?
你連最后一點理智都沒了么
Don't.
別動
l need to use the chair.
我需要用那張椅子
l offer no aid to one side or the other.
我不會幫任何一邊
-The balance. -Screw the balance.
- 平衡 - 去他媽的平衡
You dare? ln my house?
你敢？在我這儿？
ls this neutral? Bullshit.
這也叫中立嗎？狗屁！
You're the only one still playing by the rules, Midnite.
米耐，你是唯一一個還在按規矩做的人！
And while you've been imitating Switzerland, people are dying.
當你保持中立的時候 人們卻在死去
Hennessy, Beeman, they were your friends once too, remember?
亨尼斯，比曼，他們曾經都是你的朋友 你不記得了么？
l need your help!
我需要你的幫助！
Consider it a last request.
就當是最后的請求
You play a dangerous game.
你太冒險了
Two-hundred-dollar shirt, by the way.
這件襯衫可要200美元
That little shit has been trying to climb out of his father's shadow for eons.
那個小畜牲早就想走出 他父親的陰影了
l'd hate to think what he would do to this world if he ever broke through.
不敢想象要是他沖破結界的話 世界會變成什么樣
Forgot how big it was.
都忘了它有這么大
Two hundred souls passed through this wood and steel at Sing Sing.
在紐約新新監獄里 這張椅子曾經拷問了200個靈魂
Yeah.
是的
Which way's east?
哪邊是東？
How many years since you've surfed?
多久沒沖浪了？
Like riding a bike.
就像騎自行車
No, not really.
沒那么輕松
Tell me this isn't about the girl.
希望這不是為了那女孩
Definitely mostly not about the girl.
絕對主要不是為了那女孩
Cold.
好冷
Little flavor?
來一口？
-Sure about this? -No.
- 准備好了？ - 不
Midnite!
米耐！
-Any luck? -That's a word for it.
- 找到了么？ - 找到了
Holy shit. You're Papa Midnite, aren't you?
老天，這不是米耐老爹嗎？
And how exactly do you intend on getting close enough to use these?
你到底打算怎么用這些？ 要离得很近才行
Well, they did not leave her unguarded.
她的周圍肯定有人守衛
Half-breeds are most vulnerable. . .
當雜种的外皮被圣水澆裂之后
. . .when their outer skin is breached by holy water.
他們是非常脆弱的
Certain objects, most notably either of the two crosses of lsteria. . .
可以用某些圣物 特別是伊斯塔利亞十字架
. . .have been used by even the unordained to bless. . .
即使是沒有正式受命的牧師 也可以用它來把……
. . .commonly occurring waters. . .
普通的水……
. . .even rain.
甚至是雨水，變成圣水
Maybe if. . . .
也許如果……
There's no use sitting on the bench if you're not ready to play, right?
如果沒有為比賽做好准備 干坐在候補席上也是沒用的，對嗎？
You wouldn't have one of those enchanted crosses here in a cabinet. . .
我們為什么不從櫥柜里 拿一支施有魔法的十字架
. . .maybe we could take with us?
帶在身上用呢？
Look, John, no offense, l just don't think that it's a great idea, you know. . .
約翰，我無意冒犯 我只是提點建議，我覺得……
. . .you going on a solo mission to save the world. That's my vote.
你這樣單槍匹馬去拯救世界 這么做并不聰明
l don't know what pops thinks, but that's--
我不知道他怎么想 可是……
Take him, John. Kill him after.
把他帶上吧，約翰 完事之后再把他殺了
lf you get back, see me about membership. Maybe.
如果你能回來 來找我，或許我能讓你成為會員
Okay. l will.
好的，我會的
-What are you doing? -Praying.
- 你在干嘛？ - 祈禱
Praying. Okay.
祈禱，好吧
Come on.
來吧
Half-breeds, right?
雜种，對嗎？
A birth like this, they're definitely gonna be guarding her, right? Definitely.
他們肯定守護著她，對嗎？ 肯定是的
Yeah.
對
We can get through them. l mean, that cross has gotta work, right?
我們能夠解決他們 我是說，十字架會起作用的，對嗎？
Right?
對嗎？
lt's not always like it is in the books.
現實和書本不完全一樣
What is that?
那是什么？
Hellspeak.
地獄的聲音
You know what to do.
你知道該怎么做了
l'm okay.
沒問題
Sure.
好的
One last show.
最后一次演出
Hi.
嗨
My name's John.
我的名字叫約翰
You are in violation of the balance.
你們破坏了平衡
Leave immediately. . .
立刻离開
. . .or l will deport you.
否則，我將把你們驅逐
All of you.
你們所有的人
Go to hell.
去死吧
Holy water?
圣水？
Angela.
安吉拉
John?
約翰？
John.
約翰
Shit.
媽的
Pull!
拉住！
Angela.
安吉拉
Angela, what is it?
安吉拉，怎么了？
Get it out.
把它赶出來
Get it--
把它……
Oh, my God.
哦，上帝
Not bad, kid.
干得不賴，孩子
''Not bad. '' You hear that?
“干得不賴” 你听到了嗎？
You know why that is? lt's because this is Kramer. Chas Kramer, ass--
知道為什么嗎？因為我是克萊默 查斯·克萊默，混……
Chas.
查斯
You're right, John.
你說得沒錯，約翰
lt's not like the books.
和書上不一樣
No. . .
不……
. . .it isn't.
不一樣
lnto the light, l command thee.
現身吧，我命令你
Your ego is astounding.
你的能量令我吃惊
Gabriel.
加百列
Figures.
不出所料
And the wicked shall inherit the Earth.
邪惡將接管地球
You judging me now, John?
你是在審判我嗎？約翰
Betrayal, murder, genocide, call me provincial.
背叛，謀殺，种族滅絕 卻說我狹隘
l am simply seeking to inspire mankind to all that was intended.
我只是想喚醒人類 讓他們看到后果
By handing Earth over to the son of the devil?
通過把地球拱手讓給惡魔之子？
Help me here.
殺了我吧
You're handed this precious gift, right?
你被賦予了這种寶貴的天賦，對嗎？
Each one of you granted redemption from the Creator.
造物主允許你們每個人贖罪
Murderers, rapists and molesters. . .
殺人犯，強奸犯，性騷扰……
. . .all of you, you just have to repent. . .
你們所有這些人 只要忏悔
. . .and God takes you into his bosom.
上帝就會伸出雙手迎接你們
ln all the worlds in all the universe. . .
茫茫宇宙，大千世界
. . .no other creature can make such a boast, save man.
除了人類以外 沒有哪种生物能以此為傲
lt's not fair.
這不公平
lf sweet, sweet God loves you so. . .
如果好心的上帝這么愛你們
. . .then l'll make you worthy of his love.
那我就要讓你們值得被他愛
l've been watching you for a long time.
我盯著你很久了
lt's only in the face of horror that you truly find your nobler selves.
只有面對恐懼的時候 你才能真正找到你高貴的自我
And you can be so noble.
你才能變得那么的高貴
So. . .
因此
. . .l'll bring you pain.
我要給你帶來痛苦
l'll bring you horror.
帶來恐懼
So that you may rise above it.
這樣你才能戰胜它們
So that those of you who survive this reign of hell on Earth. . .
這樣，那些從人間地獄中存活下來的人
. . .will be worthy of God's love.
才值得擁有上帝的愛
Gabriel. . .
加百列
. . .you're insane.
你瘋了
The road to salvation begins tonight.
拯救將在今晚展開
Right now.
就現在
l know l'm not one of your favorites.
我知道你不喜歡我
l'm not even welcome in your house.
你甚至不歡迎我進你的家門
But l could use a little attention.
我能引起你些許的注意嗎？
Please.
懇求你
Come forth.
來吧
Hurry.
快點
Mammon. . .
曼蒙……
. . .son of Satan. . .
撒旦之子
. . .l unleash you unto this world.
我來把你放入這個世界
Lu.
路
What took you so long?
為什么這么久才來
Hello, John.
你好，約翰
You're the one soul. . .
你的靈魂
. . .l would come up here to collect myself.
我是一定要親自來收的
So l've heard.
我听說了
You mind?
不介意吧？
Oh, go-- Go right ahead. l've got stock.
哦，可以，隨意 我有時間
Coffin nail.
香煙
Very fitting, John.
和你很配，約翰
You know, when you cut too deep, you cut the tendons. . .
知道嗎，割得太深會割斷肌腱
. . .finger movement goes out the window.
手指就不听使喚了
Let me help you.
我來幫你
See?
看到了嗎？
Sonny. . .
小寶貝……
. . .l've got a whole theme park full of red delights for you.
我為你准備了一整座主題公園 讓你好好快活
Well, aren't you a peach.
哦，你真好
l didn't think you would make the same mistake twice.
我想，你不會再犯同樣的錯誤了吧
And you didn't. . .
你不會的
. . .did you?
是不是？
So how's the family?
你家里都好嗎？
Family's doing just fine. Busy, busy, busy. Need a vacation.
很好 忙得要命，需要休個假了
Word is that kid of yours is a chip off the old block.
听說你的孩子和你一個脾气
Well, one does what one can.
是啊，個頂個的棒
He's in the other room.
他就在隔壁
Boys will be boys.
男孩就是男孩
With Gabriel.
和加百列在一起
No accounting for taste, really.
有些愛好真的沒法解釋
They have the Spear of Destiny.
他們拿著命運之矛
''They have the Spear of Destiny. ''
“他們拿著命運之矛”
Or is it another one of your cons?
又想和我玩什么花樣？
Go look for yourself.
你自己去看
You've waited 20 years for me, Lu. . .
路，你已經等了我20年
. . .what's another 20 seconds?
再等20秒又何妨？
-Lucifer. -This world is mine. ln time.
- 路西法 - 這個世界是我的，幸虧及時赶到
You, best of all of us, Gabriel. . .
你，加百列 作為我們之中最棒的
. . .should understand ambition.
居然也這么有野心
Son of perdition.
毀滅之子
Little horn.
小喇叭
Most unclean.
最邪惡的人
l do miss the old names.
真怀念這些舊時的稱呼
Time to go home, son.
該回家了，儿子
l will smite thee. . .
我要替上帝
. . .in his honor.
懲罰你
Looks like somebody doesn't have your back anymore.
好像某人不再支持你了
Father?
父親？
So.
那么
Yeah, what do you want? An extension?
好了，你想要什么？ 再給你延期？
The sister. . .
她的妹妹
. . .lsabel.
伊莎貝爾
What about her?
她怎么了？
Let her go home.
讓她回家
You're willing to give up your life so she can go to heaven?
你愿意放棄你的生命 讓她升入天堂？
Fine. lt's done.
好的，可以
Time to go, John.
該走了，約翰
Yeah.
好的
The sacrifice.
獻身
No. This one belongs to me.
不，這個人屬于我
No. You will live, John Constantine.
不，你要活著，約翰·康斯坦丁
You will live.
你要活著
So you will have. . .
這樣你才……
. . .the chance to prove. . .
有机會證明
. . .that your soul truly belongs in hell.
你的靈魂是屬于地獄的
Oh, you will live.
哦，你要活著
You will live.
你要活著
Thank you.
謝謝你
No problem.
沒關系
Human.
人類
You don't deserve to be human.
你不應該成為人類
Do you want revenge? ls that what you're thinking right now?
你想報仇嗎？ 你現在是這么想的嗎？
Do it.
來吧
Seek revenge.
替他們報仇吧
End my life.
殺了我吧
Go on.
來啊
Be the hand of God.
替上帝動手吧
lt's your choice.
這是你的選擇
lt's always been your choice.
一直都是你的選擇
Yeah.
好吧
That's called pain.
這叫做痛
Get used to it.
學著習慣吧
You could've shot me, John!
你本可以打死我的，約翰！
You chose a higher path!
你選擇了積德！
Look how well you're doing!
看你做得多棒！
Nice spot.
景色不錯
l have something for you.
我有東西要給你
Something tells me you're not a flowers kind of guy.
這樣東西讓我知道 你不是那种華而不實的人
Oh, how thoughtful.
哦，你真聰明
John. . .
約翰
. . .why are you giving me this?
為什么給我這個？
Rules.
這是規則
Hide it.
把它藏起來
Somewhere no one will ever be able to find it.
藏在一個沒人能找到的地方
Not even me.
包括我
Always a catch.
就知道沒那么簡單
Yeah.
是啊
So.
那么
l've got some cleaning up to do.
我想洗個澡
l'll. . .
我們……
. . .see you around.
再見吧
l'd like that.
好啊
I guess there's a plan for all of us.
我想，我們每個人都自有安排
I had to die...
我死了兩次
... twice...
才明白
...just to figure that out.
這個道理
Like the book says, he works his work in mysterious ways.
就像書上說的，冥冥中自有安排
Some people like it...
有些人喜歡
...some people don 't.
有些人不喜歡
You did good, kid.
你做得很好，孩子
Subtitles by SDl Media Group
TLF中文字幕站 http://tlfsubs.eastgame.net